Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
- Faculty, Staff, Administrators - Photographs
  - S-Z
    - Taylor, William R. -- Botany (Box 20)
    - Teal, Laurence L. -- Wind Instruments (Box 20)
    - Thieme, Frederick -- ? (Box 20)
    - Thomas, Edwin J. -- Social Work (Box 20)
    - Thomas, Norman C. -- Political Science (Box 20)
    - Thomas, Morgan -- Political Science (Box 20)
    - Thompson, Clyde H. -- Double Bass (Box 20)
    - Thrall, Robert M. -- Math (Box 20)
    - Thuma, Burton D. -- Asst. Dean (Box 20)
    - Tikofsky, Ronald S. -- Speech (Box 20)
    - Tippitt, Ronald -- Psychology, Sociology (Box 20)
    - Tirrell, John E. -- Alumni Association (Box 20)
    - Tonsor, Stephen J. -- History (Box 20)
    - Torrens, James -- ? (Box 20)
    - Tracy, John E. -- Law (Box 20)
    - Trost, Robert W. -- Military Science (Box 20)
    - Tupper, Charles John -- Internal Medicine (Box 20)
    - Turneaure, Frederick S. -- Geology (Box 20)
    - Uhlenbeck, George E. -- Physics (Box 20)
    - Uhr, Leonard M. -- Mental Health (Box 20)
    - Upham, Lucille W. -- League (Box 20)
    - Valusek, John E. -- Reading Improvement Service (Box 20)
    - Vance, Kenneth E. -- Consultant (Box 20)
    - VandenBroek, Jan -- Engineering (Box 20)
    - Vandermade, Minor, Jr. -- University Hospital (Box 20)
    - Van der Schalie, Henry -- Zoology (Box 20)
    - Van Vlack, Lawrence H. -- Metallurgical Eng (Box 20)
    - Van Wylen, Gordon J. -- Mechanical Eng (Box 20)
    - Vaughan, Henry F. -- Public Health (Box 20)
    - Veroff, Joseph -- Psychology, Survey Research Ctr (Box 20)
    - Vial, Alexander B. -- Surgery (Box 20)
    - Vidar, Frede J. -- Drawing (Box 20)
    - Vincent, Donald E. -- Dearborn Library (Box 20)
    - Vincent, Edward T. -- Engineering (Box 20)
    - Vinter, Robert D. -- Social Work (Box 20)
    - Vroman, Clyde -- Music Education, Admissions (Box 20)
    - Walcott, Fred G. -- Education (Box 20)
    - Walter, Erich A. -- Asst. to President, English (Box 20)
    - Ward, Robert E. -- Political Science (Box 20)
    - Ward, Stanley A. -- Registration (Box 20)
    - Warner, Robert A. -- Music (Box 20)
    - Warner, Robert M. -- Michigan Historical Collections (Box 20)
    - Warner, Sam -- History (Box 20)
    - Warshaw, Martin R. -- Marketing (Box 20)
    - Waterman, Leroy -- Semitics (Box 20)
    - Waterman, Merwin H. -- Finance (Box 20)
    - Watkins, Herbert G. -- Secretary, Asst. Vice President (Box 20)
    - Watkins, Leonard L. -- Economics (Box 20)
    - Weaver, Bennett -- English (Box 20)
    - Weaver, Richard L. -- Conservation (Box 20)
    - Weeks, Robert P. -- English (Box 20)
    - Wegman, Myron E. -- Dean of Pub. Health (Box 20)
    - Weichlein, William J. -- Music Literature (Box 20)
    - Weimar, David -- English (Box 20)
    - Weimar, John -- English (Box 20)
    - Weir, Don A. -- Ticket Manager (Box 20)
    - Weller, C. V. -- ? (Box 20)
    - Weinberg, Gerhard -- History (Box 20)
    - Wells, Carlton F. -- English (Box 20)
    - Wentzel, Donat G. -- Astronomy (Box 20)
    - Wernette, John P. -- Business Admin (Box 20)
    - Westerman, Walter S., Jr. -- Education (Box 20)
    - Wethey, Harold -- History of Art (Box 20)
    - White, Ink -- Regent (Box 20)
    - White, John P. -- Political Science (Box 20)
    - Wehrer, Joseph J. -- Arch. & Design (Box 20)
    - White, Leslie A. -- Anthropology (Box 20)
    - White, Robert R. -- Chemical Eng (Box 20)
    - White, William T. -- Alumni Association (Box 20)
    - Whitehouse, Walter M. -- Radiology (Box 20)
    - Whiting, Allen -- Political Science (Box 20)
    - Whittemore, Harlow O. -- Architecture (Box 20)
    - Wiegand, Bill -- English (Box 20)
    - Wilder, Raymond L. -- Math (Box 20)
    - Wilensky, Harold L. -- Sociology (Box 20)
    - Wilhelm, Ross -- Business Economics (Box 20)
    - Willcox, William -- History (Box 20)
    - Willman, Richard V. -- Law (Box 20)
    - Willson, Robert -- Gynecology, Obstetrics (Box 20)
    - Wilson, Gayle C. -- Admissions (Box 20)
    - Wilson, James Tinley -- Geology, IST (Box 20)
    - Wingo, Glenn Max -- Education (Box 20)
    - Wit, Daniel -- Political Science (Box 20)
    - Withey, Stephen B. -- Psychology (Box 20)
    - Wolfgang, Leonard -- History, Russian Studies (Box 20)
    - Woodburne, Russell T. -- Anatomy (Box 20)
    - Wooding, Edmund -- Journalism (Box 20)
    - Woodland, Arthur E. -- Zoology (Box 20)
    - Woodworth, G. Walter -- Business Admin (Box 20)
    - Work, Walter P. -- Medical School (Box 20)
    - Wright, Lafayette Hart -- Law (Box 20)
    - Wyatt, Frederick -- Psychology (Box 20)
    - Wyllie, Cleland B. -- Education, Info & News Srvc (Box 20)
    - Yamagiwa, Joseph K. -- Japanese (Box 20)
    - Yates, Donald R. -- Romance Languages (Box 20)
    - Yntema, Hessel E. -- Comparative Law (Box 20)
    - Young, Earnest -- ? (Box 20)
    - Young, Gail S. -- Math (Box 20)
    - Young, Raymond J. -- Higher Education (Box 20)
    - Youtie, Herbert C. -- Papyrology (Box 20)
    - Youtz, Philip N. -- Dean of Architecture and Design (Box 20)
    - Zamiska, L. -- Arch. & Design (Box 20)
    - Zander, Alvin F. -- Educational Psych (Box 20)
    - Zeisler, Karl F. -- Journalism (Box 20)
    - Zerman, Bill -- Fraternities (Box 20)
    - Zumberge, James H. -- Geology (Box 20)
- Negatives-Topical, 1968-1982; 3.5 linear feet
  The series Negatives, 1968-1982, (3.5 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by subject. Dates given when known. Each entry is a single envelope of negatives unless otherwise noted. Because several subjects are often contained on a single strip of film, "See" and "See also" cross-references may refer to seemingly unrelated subjects. Researchers should look at the envelope containing the negatives for more details. Photographers who contributed many negatives to this series include Bell, Benjamin, Bilinsky, Engstrom, Fink, Freeberg, Hagen, Harris, Lubers, McMahon, O'Malley, and Schneider. Photographers are sometimes but not always indicated on the envelopes.
  - A-C (Box 21)
    - Abzug, Bella (Box 21)
    - Ackley and Fusfeld (economics professors), October 30, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Adams (Box 21)
      (See-Solomon)
    - Agnew, Spiro T (Box 21)
    - Aldridge, Blasi, Hagan (professors), January 16, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Alpha Chi Alpha (Box 21)
    - Ali, Mohammed, October 30, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Allan (city council candidate) (Box 21)
      (See-Greenburgh)
    - Allen, John (Residential College Professor), January 15, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Allende, Isabel, November 18, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Alligators (Natural Science program), February 7, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Amini, Katayoon, January, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Amtrak, March, May, and June, 1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Andelli, January 17, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Anderson, Thomas, September 29, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Ann Arbor Art Fair, 1979-1982; 11 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Flood)
    - Ann Arbor City Council and candidates 7 envelopes, 1977-1981 (Box 21)
      (See also-Athletics--Track--Men's and names of individual council members and candidates
    - Ann Arbor judge, February 15, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Ann Arbor locations (streets, parks, etc.), 1980-1982; 12 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Bullard, Perry)
    - Ann Arbor mayoral debate (Box 21)
    - Ann Arbor Transit Authority, 1980-1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Simonetta, Richard)
    - Annie cinematographer, April 14, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Arboretum (Box 21)
      (See also-Morris Dancers)
    - Arborland Art Fair (Box 21)
      (See-Burns Park fire)
    - Army (rappelling off Dentistry Building), November 6, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Arnson, Eric (Michigan Student Assembly president), January 31, 1978; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Arroyo press conference (economics building arsonist), February 16, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Art, University of Michigan School of, Mills/O'Connor art exhibit at Slusser Gallery, February 7, 1980 (Box 21)
    - "Art of the Sixties" exhibit, November 13, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Ashcroft, Rick (concrete canoe mold), January 20, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Ashmore, Harry, October 20, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Astronomy chairman, October 8, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Athletics (University of Michigan teams except where noted)
      - Athletic Committee, October 29, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Baseball
        - 1980-81, 20 envelopes (Box 21)
        - Detroit Tigers, April 14, 1981 (Box 21)
        - Summer camp, June 17, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Basketball
        - Men's, 1979-1981; 9 envelopes (Box 21)
        - Women's, 1977; 1979; 1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
          (See also- Track - Women's
      - Boxing, November 16, 1982 (Box 21)
      - Eastern Michigan University rally, November 19, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Football
        - Games, 1976-1981; 44 envelopes (Box 21)
        - Players (still shots), 1980-1981; 6 envelopes (Box 21)
        - Slippery Rock v. Shippenberg, September 29, 1979; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
        - "Whiskey the Football Dog" (Box 21)
      - Gymnastics, 1979-1980; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
      - Hockey
        (See also-Howe, Gordie)
        - 1980, 3 envelopes (Box 21)
        - "Polish Hockey,", June 2, 1980 (Box 21)
      - Rugby, October 10, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Scholarship presentation, 1981 (Box 21)
        (See-Unicyclist)
      - Softball, April 3, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Swimming, Women's (Box 21)
      - Tennis, Men's, May 10, 1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
      - Track
        - Men's, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
        - Women's, 1981-1982; 4 envelopes (Box 21)
        - Ann Arbor, women's, February 20, 1982 (Box 21)
      - Volleyball, 1980-1981; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
      - Wrestling, 1980-1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Atkinson, Grace, February 25, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Auction, May 16, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Austin (Box 21)
      (See-Claybrook)
    - Auton, Diane, March 23, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Baba and Friends, October 3, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Baker, Deane (Regent), November 18, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Baird, Steven (guitarist on Diag), October 24, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Band, University of Michigan Marching, 1978-1981; 5 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Bardwich, Judith (Dean), October 29, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Barks, Coleman (poet), November 13, 1972; March 1974; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Baro, Gene, January 19, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Bartending course, Union University Club, December 4, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Bayh, Birch (Senator from Indiana), October 27, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Beaver, Frank (film professor), February 13, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van (bust) (Box 21)
    - Belcher, Louis, 1976-1981; 8 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Trowbridge, Ron
    - Belkamp (Box 21)
    - Bell, Derrick (desegregation seminar), March 19, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Bell, Gerald, April 2, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Bell, Griffin, 2 envelopes
      - Bell, 1977 (Box 21)
      - Hearing, with shot of Ted Kennedy (Box 21)
    - Beltz, Doug (hypnotist), July 22, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ben-Gurion, David (Box 21)
    - Benson, James (energy analyst of ERDA), April 29, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Bentley, Tom (SEC Lawyer), September 20, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Benvenisti, Meron, November 5, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Bergland (senator) (Box 21)
    - Bergmann, Frithjof (philosophy professor), May 5, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Bergstrom, George, March 27, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Berneau (?), Ben (Box 21)
      (See-Stephanapolous, Stacy)
    - Bernies, Ken, February 27, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Berry, Lee (musician), May 26, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Besozzi, Myrwood (nuclear cardiologist), December 4, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Beyard, Jaky (?) (jazz pianist), November 20, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Bier, Alan, April 11, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Bivouac (Ann Arbor store), 1980-1981; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Blasi (Box 21)
      (See-Aldridge)
    - Block, Joel, September 27, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Blood donation, 1979; 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Blow, James, March 30, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Blue Front owners, August 14, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Bluestone, Irving (Vice President, United Auto Workers), February 8, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Blum (Ambassador from Israel to the United Nations), November 13, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Blumenthal, AIESEC (?), March 14, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Body building (Box 21)
    - Bond, Julian, 1975; 1979; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Booth, Jon and Marcia (International Center workers), January 31, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Bowen, Lisa, February 12, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Braccy, Warren, January 10, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Breakstone, Mark (Box 21)
      (See-Witt, Howard)
    - Brickman, May 18, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Bright, Charles (Assistant Professor of History, Residential College), November 11, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Brinkerhoff, James (University Vice President and Chief Financial Officer), September 27, 1977; November 15, 1977; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Brodsky, Josef (Soviet poet), 1972-1974; 4 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Bromberg, April 17,1980 (Box 21)
    - Brooks, Gwen (Box 21)
      (See-Pena)
    - Brooks, Lonnie (blues singer), January 14, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Brorson, Bill (Democratic council candidate) (Box 21)
    - Broughten, Mike (Democratic council candidate), April 2, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Brown, Harold (Secretary of Defense during Carter Administration) (Box 21)
    - Brown, John (Peace Corps), March 23, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Brown, Woody, 1977; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Brownmiller, Susan, March 22, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Bryant, Don, January 31, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (political science educator and official of the National Security Council under President Jimmy Carter), September 19, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Buban, Ben, September 21, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Buckley, William F., October 3, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Budweiser Clydesdale horses, September 25, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Buford (unicyclist), April 9, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Bukovsky, Vladimir, November 18, 1977; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Bullard, Joanna, January, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Bullard, Perry, 1972-1980; 10 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Amtrak; Milliken, William)
    - Burchett, December 7, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Burghardt (Box 21)
      (See-Bullard, Perry)
    - Burns Park fire, October 3, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Burns, Eunice (Ann Arbor City Council member, Chair of Women's Commission) (Box 21)
    - Burris, Carol (National Women's Lobby), April 14, 1977; January 10, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Bursley, Gilbert (Senator), October 20 (no year), January 28, 1972; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Burton, Toni, February 26, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Burton Tower (Box 21)
    - CIA rally (Box 21)
      (See-Sinclair's brother)
    - Calduone (?), Dr. ("Sex and the Handicapped" lecture), November 13, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Campbell, Angus (ISR Director), April 15, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Campbell, Mrs. Gene, April 11, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Campbell, Richard (Box 21)
    - Canham (Box 21)
      (See-Milliken)
    - Cappaert, Leroy (city council, 5th ward), January 19, 1978; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Carr, Bob, March 9, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Carter, Jimmy, October 21, 1977; 4 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Cavanaugh, Jerome (mayor of Detroit), July 12, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Chan, David (Playboy photographer), March 18, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Chapin, Harry (Box 21)
    - Charity ("Fraternity collecting canned goods for Ann Arbor needy"), November 13, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Chavez, Cesar, July 1973; November 1979; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Cheerleaders (Box 21)
      (See-Blue Front owners)
    - Chesborough, Joyce, March 30, 1982 (Box 21)
    - China Garden (restaurant), January, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Chisolm, Shirley (Box 21)
    - Chorea (pianist), March 21, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Christian, Chris, February, 1974; November 15, 1974; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Christianson, April 5, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Christopher, February 27, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Cicerono (at Chrysler Research Lab) (Box 21)
    - Clark, Jerry ("and strike"), February 13, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Clark, Perry, January 30, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Clark, Ramsey, October 30, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Clarke, Arthur, April 10, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Claybrook and Austin (Box 21)
    - Cmejrek, James (5th ward city council candidate), January 31, 1978 (Box 21)
      (See also-Cohen, Wilbur)
    - Cobb, J. (sign), September 12, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Cobb, January 15, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Cobb, Jewel (Box 21)
    - Cockrell ("Free Art") and Dr. Tom Minter (Box 21)
    - Cohen, Carl, September 30, 1977; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Cohen, Jeff, November 21, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Cohen, Wilbur (Education School Dean), January 31, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Col, Al, April 29, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Colburn, C. William, 1974-1978; 4 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Comauo (SWP President), March 28, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Commager, Henry Steele (historian), October 8, 1970 (Box 21)
    - Commencement (Box 21)
      (See-Graduation)
    - Commoner, Barry, February 21, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Computers, 1979; 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Confora, Alan (Kent State), October 19, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Conneli (?) (with "Sesame Street kids"), February 19, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Connely (?) (Ann Arbor City Council member) (Box 21)
    - "Continental Divide hikers", June 2, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Coones (Box 21)
    - Cooper, Admiral., October 8, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Co-operative housing, 1979; 1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also- Flood
    - Corbett, Dr. (author), August 5, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Cracked Crab (restaurant), March 23, 1981 (Box 21)
    - CRISP (student registration system), 1980-1981; 3 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Shorten, Ted
    - Cronyn, Hume and Jessica Tandy, October 17, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Crouch, Gay, December 6, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Calley, William, Lt (Box 21)
    - Cousteau, Jacques, October 7, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Cullen, Bernard (Irish), February 9, 1972 (Box 21)
  - D-G
    - Dagostino, Rose (Michigan League cafeteria) (Box 21)
    - Dai Lai, October 11, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Daley, Richard (Mayor), August 1968 (Box 21)
    - Davidoff, March 25, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Davids, Col. (Safety Pit), January 13, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Davis, Garry, January 17, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Davis, Rennie (Box 21)
    - Davis, Skeeta, October 11, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Davis (mother of Angela Davis), January 27, 1972 (Box 21)
    - Day in the Death of Joe Egg, A (play), February 9, 1977 (Box 21)
    - De Larrocha, Alicia (Box 21)
    - Dean, John, November 16, 1977; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Deere, Phillip (Muskoke Indian), October 12, 1977 (Box 21)
    - De Crow, Karen (President of N.O.W.), February 22, 1977; undated; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Delhey, William (County Prosecutor), September 14, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Dellums, Ronald (California House State Representative), February 22, 1977; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Demonstrations, protests, etc., 18 envelopes
      (See also-Graduate Employees Organization, Kolossos strike, Michigan Student Assembly, Regents, Word processors
      - Nuclear power, September 28, 1979 (Box 21)
      - Iran, November 20, 1979 (Box 21)
      - Cambodia, January 16, 1980 (Box 21)
      - Draft and war, 1980-1981; 5 envelopes (Box 21)
        (See also Bullard, Perry)
      - NOW, June 1981 (Box 21)
      - "Solidarity,", January 7, 1982 (Box 21)
      - El Salvador, March 1981-January 1982; 4 envelopes (Box 21)
      - Boycott of "Dress to Kill,", March 14, 1981 (Box 21)
      - Abortion, May 14, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Denver, John (speech on world hunger at the Michigan Theater), April 11, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Derezenski (Senate candidate), February 9, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Dial, Stephen, October 25, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Diggs, Charles (Congressman), March 13, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Dooleys (bar), March 16, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Dorse, Norman (?), October 4, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Douvan, Elizabeth (of the Psychology Department and Institute for Social Research), August 11, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Drag show (Box 21)
      (See-Col, Al)
    - Drugs, October 10, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Dubois, David, November 1975 (Box 21)
    - Duderstadt, James (Dean, College of Engineering), July 23, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Earle, The (restaurant, with band), January 12, 1978 (Box 21)
    - East Quad cafeteria (Box 21)
      (See-Brown, Woody)
    - Eastbound, January 28, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Easthope, Tom (Ombudsman), March 31, 1978; July 31, 1979; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
      (See also-Frye, Billy)
    - Ebony, Mr (Box 21)
    - Economic Outlook conference, November 29, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Economics professors (including Weisskopf) (Box 21)
    - Eckstein (professor) (Box 21)
    - Education, School of (Children's Play Center) (Box 21)
    - Ehrlichman, John, John Fowles, and H.R. Haldeman, October 19, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Eklund, Susan (Assistant Law School Dean), September 23 and 27, 1976; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Elder, Madelyn, March 22, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Eldon, Samuel (judge) (Box 21)
    - Elections
      - Mary Markley voters, 1979 (Box 21)
        (See-Mekenev)
      - Voter registration, November 10, 1979 (Box 21)
      - "Election party,", November 4, 1980; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
      - Carter-Mondale organizational meeting, October 2, 1980 (Box 21)
      - Reagan-Bush campaign, October 8, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Elger, R., January 24, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Ellington, Duke (band), September 24, 1978; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Ellis, Albert (sex researcher) (Box 21)
    - Elton, Robert, February 7, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Emery, Allan (Associate Director of Computer Center), June 8, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Employee Credit Union (Box 21)
    - Energy Conference, March 28, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Engineering (monument, games), March-April, 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, August 1, 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Equal Rights Amendment Walkathon, 1980 (Box 21)
    - Erickson, Nancy, November 9, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Ericson, May 19, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ervin, Sam (Senator), July 28, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Esch, Marvin (Congressman), 1975-1976; 5 envelopes (Box 21)
    - Evans, Walker (photographer) (Box 21)
    - Faber (Democratic Committee Chairman), June 7, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Fader, Lester (professor), September 25, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Falk, November 1,1979 (Box 22)
    - Fashion (Box 22)
    - Fauri, N.P., February 12, 1971; May 19, 1971; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Feldkamp, John (Box 22)
    - Ferency, Zolton, October 13, 1971; February 9, 1977; undated; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Feverman (Box 22)
    - Fieger, March 9, 1982 (Box 22)
    - Financial aid, July and September, 1981; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Fink, Ken (Box 22)
    - Fire ("next to Blimpy Burgers") (Box 22)
    - Fire Department, February 26, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Fisher, Max, February 2, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Fisher ("candidate") (Box 22)
    - Fitzgerald (Senator, candidate for Governor), December 9, 1977; January 13, 1978; June 15, 1978; 3 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Fleming, Robben (University President), 11 envelopes
      - undated (Box 22)
      - With Kennedy, January 27, 1975 (Box 22)
      - February 19, 1976 (Box 22)
      - At tea reception, September 28, 1977 (Box 22)
      - October 3, 1977 (Box 22)
      - At West Quad Cafeteria, December 5, 1977 (Box 22)
      - CIA debate vs. Kevin Stears (VSA), February 18, 1978 (Box 22)
      - At Bates, March 21, 1978 (Box 22)
      - May 17, 1978 (Box 22)
      - August 2, 1978 (Box 22)
      - Testimonial Dinner, January 24, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Flint, University of Michigan campus, July 17, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Flood, November 8, 1980; January 12, 1982; 2 envelopes (Box 22)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1936-1978; 22 envelopes
      - Football pictures, 1936 (Box 22)
      - Grand Rapids visit, January 17, 1974; 5 envelopes (Box 22)
      - January 31, 1975, 2 envelopes (Box 22)
      - J. L. Vinson, "Ford shootout,", August 1, 1975 (Box 22)
      - October 1975, 2 envelopes (Box 22)
      - At Crisler Arena, September 15, 1976; 6 envelopes (Box 22)
      - At Willow Run Airport, April 4, 1977 (Box 22)